A Guide to the Olive Chadeayne Architectural Collection, 1924-1956
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series II: Project Records.
  - Unidentified Residence, Sketch - Exterior (unknown location; undated; Residential; Olive Chadeayne) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 15 Folder Unidentified Residence, Sketch, Small House (unknown location; undated; Residential; Olive Chadeayne ) [DR] D15F23 22)
  - Unidentified Residence, Sketch, Small House (unknown location; undated; Residential; Olive Chadeayne) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 15 Folder 23)
  - Wagenbach (Encitas, CA; 1939; Residential; Olive Chadeayne) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 14 Folder 13)
  - Waite (Solana Beach, CA; 1938; Residential; Lilian Rice) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 13 Folder 8)
  - Wanner (Encitas, CA; 1940; Residential; Olive Chadeayne) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 14 Folder Weikman (Solana Beach, CA; 1938; Residential; Lilian Rice & Olive Chadeayne (assoc.) ) [DR] D14F10 16)
  - Weikman (Solana Beach, CA; 1938; Residential; Lilian Rice & Olive Chadeayne (assoc.)) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawe 14 Folder Wells (Rancho Santa Fe, CA; 1940; Residential; Olive Chadeayne ) [DR] D14F15 10)
  - Wells (Rancho Santa Fe, CA; 1940; Residential; Olive Chadeayne) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 14 Folder 15)
  - Wykoff (Glendale, CA; 1946; Residential; Olive Chadeayne) [DR]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 14 Folder 18)
- Series III: Arts & Artifacts.
  Series III: Arts & Artifacts (1927-1937) contains one watercolor drawing of the Townley residence and one historical color map of Monterey, California.
  - Townley - Proposed Remodeling of Stable (unknown location; 1937; Watercolor - exterior & floor plan, cardboard mounted; Olive Chadeayne) [AA]. (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Historical Color Map of Monterey, CA (uknown location; 1927; Map) [AA]. (Map-case MC 32 Drawer 1 Folder 24)